Guide to the Papers of Abby Weed Grey 1922-1978 MC.151
New York University Archives
- Series XVII: Abby Weed Grey Photographs, 57650
  - Subseries A: Exhibitions 1962-1972, 57699
    - University of Tehran Foundry, Students Exhibit, undated; 57714 (Box 38, Folder 6)
      - Studio Kiln, 1967; AWGP_UTE_15_6_16; 227398 (Box 38, Folder 6, Item 16)
      - Abby Weed Grey Looks at Art on Exhibition, 1967; AWGP_UTE_15_6_17; 227399 (Box 38, Folder 6, Item 17)
      - Student Demonstrates Creation of Art, 1967; AWGP_UTE_15_6_18; 227400 (Box 38, Folder 6, Item 18)
      - Art Supplies of Table in Studio, 1967; AWGP_UTE_15_6_19; 227401 (Box 38, Folder 6, Item 19)
      - Students in Studio, 1967; AWGP_UTE_15_6_20; 227409 (Box 38, Folder 6, Item 20)
      - Her Imperial Empress Farah looks at artwork, 1967; AWGP_UTE_15_6_21; 227410 (Box 38, Folder 6, Item 21)
      - Sculptures in Studio, 1967; AWGP_UTE_15_6_22; 227414 (Box 38, Folder 6, Item 22)
      - Birds Eye View Exhibit Audience, 1967; AWGP_UTE_15_6_23; 227415 (Box 38, Folder 6, Item 23)
      - Group photo students and Abbey Weed Grey, 1967; AWGP_UTE_15_6_24; 227421 (Box 38, Folder 6, Item 24)
      - Gift to University of Tehran from Grey Gallery, 1967; AWGP_UTE_15_6_25; 227422 (Box 38, Folder 6, Item 25)
      - Mr. Tanavoli and Mr. Jack Garek of Pan Am Present Gift to Tehran University, 1967; AWGP_UTE_15_6_26; 227436 (Box 38, Folder 6, Item 26)
      - Exhibit Audience Listens to Speaker, 1967; AWGP_UTE_15_6_28; 227437 (Box 38, Folder 6, Item 27)
      - Audience Looks at Art Piece, 1967; AWGP_UTE_15_6_29; 227445 (Box 38, Folder 6, Item 28)
      - Group Photo of Students in Studio, 1967; AWGP_UTE_15_6_30; 227451 (Box 38, Folder 6, Item 29)
      - Photo of Dedication Plaque at University of Tehran, 1965-23-11; AWGP_UTE_15_6_31; 227456 (Box 38, Folder 6, Item 30)
      - Abby Weed Grey Looks at Exhibit, 1967; AWGP_UTE_15_6_32; 227457 (Box 38, Folder 6, Item 31)
      - Assorted Negatives of University of Tehran and Exhibit Opening (16 Sheets), 1967; AWGP_UTE_15_6_33; 227464 (Box 38, Folder 6, Item 32)
    - Communication Thru Art, 1967; 57713 (Box 38, Folder 7)
      - "Antigua" by Richard Wilt, AWGP_CTA_15_7_1; 228246 (Box 38, Folder 7, Item 1)
      - "Cats" George Suyeoka, AWGP_CTA_15_7_2; 228247 (Box 38, Folder 7, Item 2)
      - "Landscape, Spain" Thomas Strobel, AWGP_CTA_15_7_3; 228248 (Box 38, Folder 7, Item 3)
      - "Wings I" James McGarrel, AWGP_CTA_15_7_4; 228252 (Box 38, Folder 7, Item 4)
      - "Grasshopper" Max Kahn, AWGP_CTA_15_7_5; 228253 (Box 38, Folder 7, Item 5)
      - "First Flora" Ellen Lanyon, AWGP_CTA_15_&_6; 228359 (Box 38, Folder 7, Item 6)
      - "The Great Broadeast" Billy Jackson, AWGP_TCTA_15_7_7; 228360 (Box 38, Folder 7, Item 7)
      - "Tall Grass" Margo Hoff, AWGP_CTA_15_7_8; 228361 (Box 38, Folder 7, Item 8)
      - "Drawing No. 13" Carole Harrison, AWGP_CTA_15_7_9; 228362 (Box 38, Folder 7, Item 9)
      - "Wire Fence" Robert Gough, AWGP_CTA_15_7_10; 228363 (Box 38, Folder 7, Item 10)
      - "Women in Storm" Warren Doolittle, AWGP_CTA_15_7_11; 228364 (Box 38, Folder 7, Item 11)
      - "Mother and Child" Eleanor Coen, AWGP_CTA_15_7_12; 228365 (Box 38, Folder 7, Item 12)
      - "Wave Music" Lee Chesney, AWGP_CTA_15_7_13; 228366 (Box 38, Folder 7, Item 13)
      - "The Young Riders" Francis Chapin, AWGP_CTA_15_7_14; 228421 (Box 38, Folder 7, Item 14)
      - "Shore Fragments" Fred Brian, AWGP_CTA_15_7_15; 228426 (Box 38, Folder 7, Item 15)
      - "The Garden" Harry Breen, AWGP_CTA_15_7_16; 228429 (Box 38, Folder 7, Item 16)
      - "Night Cry" Barbara Aubin, AWGP_CTA_15_7_17; 228430 (Box 38, Folder 7, Item 17)
      - "Standing Women" Harold Altman, AWGP_CTA_15_7_18; 228432 (Box 38, Folder 7, Item 18)
      - "Untitled" John Wood, AWGP_CTA_15_7_19; 228440 (Box 38, Folder 7, Item 19)
      - "Origin of Species" Jack Wolsky, AWGP_CTA_15_7_20; 228441 (Box 38, Folder 7, Item 20)
      - "In the Woods" Franz Wildenhain, AWGP_CTA_15_7_21; 228541 (Box 38, Folder 7, Item 21)
      - "Pattern" John C. Wenrich, AWGP_CTA_15_7_22; 228542 (Box 38, Folder 7, Item 22)
      - "Frozen Landscape" Arnis Sarma, AWGP_CTA_15_7_23; 228544 (Box 38, Folder 7, Item 23)
      - "Untitled" Dan Rhodes, AWGP_CTA_15_7_24; 228545 (Box 38, Folder 7, Item 24)
      - "Boule Blanche" Fred Meyer, AWGP_CTA_15_7_25; 228547 (Box 38, Folder 7, Item 25)
    - Communication Thru Art, 1967; 57712 (Box 38, Folder 8)
      - "Tree" John C. Menihan, AWGP_CTA_15_8_1; 228548 (Box 38, Folder 8, Item 1)
      - "Landscape" Joan Lyons, AWGP_15_8_2; 228549 (Box 38, Folder 8, Item 2)
      - "Christmas" Joseph Hendrick, AWGP_CTA_15_8_3; 228555 (Box 38, Folder 8, Item 3)
      - "Winter Tree" Dorothy Glaser, AWGP_CTA_15_8_4; 228556 (Box 38, Folder 8, Item 4)
      - "Sodus" Kurt Feuerherm, AWGP_CTA_15_8_5; 228557 (Box 38, Folder 8, Item 5)
      - "Still Life" Alfonsas Dargis, AWGP_CTA_15_8_6; 228558 (Box 38, Folder 8, Item 6)
      - "Owl" Robert Conge, AWGP_CTA_15_8_7; 228559 (Box 38, Folder 8, Item 7)
      - "Landscape" Philip Bonarth, AWGP_CTA_15_8_8; 228560 (Box 38, Folder 8, Item 8)
      - "Composition" Bertha Bonart, AWGP_CTA_15_8_9; 228561 (Box 38, Folder 8, Item 9)
      - "Structures No. 6" Leonard Barkin, AWGP_CTA_15_8_10; 228562 (Box 38, Folder 8, Item 10)
      - "Evening Lights" Ralph Avery, AWGP_CTA_15_8_11; 228563 (Box 38, Folder 8, Item 11)
      - "Head of a Man" Richard Arnold, AWGP_CTA_15_8_12; 228564 (Box 38, Folder 8, Item 12)
      - "Summer" Milford Apetz, AWGP_CTA_15_8_13; 228565 (Box 38, Folder 8, Item 13)
      - "A Valediction of Weeping" June Wayne, AWGP_CTA_15_8_14; 228566 (Box 38, Folder 8, Item 14)
      - "We are Tapers too" June Wayne, AWGP_CTA_15_8_15; 228568 (Box 38, Folder 8, Item 15)
      - "Mirror" Beth Van Hoesen, AWGP_CTA_15_8_16; 228570 (Box 38, Folder 8, Item 16)
      - "Profile" Beth Van Hoesen, AWGP_CTA_15_8_17; 228576 (Box 38, Folder 8, Item 17)
      - "Cynthia" Beth Van Hoesen, AWGP_CTA_15_8_18; 228577 (Box 38, Folder 8, Item 18)
      - "Goldilocks" Sinton, AWGP_CTA_15_8_19; 228578 (Box 38, Folder 8, Item 19)
      - "The Wedding" Ariel Parkinson, AWGP_CTA_15_8_20; 228579 (Box 38, Folder 8, Item 20)
      - "The Family" Nancy Genn, AWGP_CTA_15_8_21; 228580 (Box 38, Folder 8, Item 21)
      - "Draped Woman in Room", AWGP_CTA_15_8_22; 228581 (Box 38, Folder 8, Item 22)
    - 1st Triennale of World Art, India, 1968; 57711 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Communication Thru Art, Indian Tour, 1968; 57710 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - M.A.P. Party, Jan 11, 1969; 57709 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Communication Thru Art, S. India, 1969; 57708 (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - 10 Young American Artists, 1970; 57707 (Box 39, Folder 1)
      3 1142 04225402 2
    - Communication Thru Art, India, Book Presentation, 1970; 57706 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - MCAD Exhibition, Installation, 1970; 57705 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Turkish Art, SUNY Binghamton, 1971; 57704 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Contemporary Turkish Painting, 1971; 57703 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - One World Thru Art, Installation, Minn State Fair, Jun 7, 1972; 57702 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - One World Thru Art -mounted, Jun 7, 1972; 57701 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - One World Thru Art -mounted, Jun 7, 1972; 57700 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Subseries B: Personal and Publicity, 57694
    - Benjamin Grey & Abby Weed Grey-Early, undated; 57698 (Box 40, Folder 1)
      3 1142 04225403 0
    - Abby Weed Grey-Publicity, undated; 57697 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Abby Weed Grey & Thomas Waite-curator, undated; 57696 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Deqhani-Tafti, Hassam (Angelican Bishop of Iran), undated; 57695 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Additions, undated; 216167 (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - Additions (Publicity), Undated; 216168 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Subseries C: Grey Gallery-St. Paul, 57692
    - Grey Gallery at 4997 Otis St., St. Paul, undated; 57693 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Subseries D: Grey Gallery-NYU, 57685
    - Opening & Collateral, undated; 57691 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Grey Art Gallery & 3rd Floor Main, undated; 57690 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Iranian Art Today, 1976; 57689 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Lion Rug Exhibit, undated; 57688 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Tanavoli Exhibit, undated; 57687 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Works Donated, 1982; 57686 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Subseries E: Artist Photos, 57674
    - Communication Thru Art, undated; 57684 (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Aslier, Mustafa & Berk, Nurullah-Turkey, undated; 57683 (Box 40, Folder 13)
      General
      The man identified as Nurullah Berk in the image may be somebody else.
    - Ayden, Necat-Turkey, undated; 57682 (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - Berger, Aliye-Turkey, undated; 57681 (Box 41, Folder 1)
      3 1142 04225404 8
    - Eyuboglu, Bedri Rahmi, undated; 57680 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Golzari, Behrooz-Iran, undated; 57679 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Jamshid, Khagam; Siah, Armanjami; Parviz, Tanavoli, 1962; 57678 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Koral, Fureya-Turkey, undated; 57677 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Kut, Mushin-Turkey, undated; 57676 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Varlik, Utku-Turkey, undated; 57675 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Subseries F: Tanavoli, Parviz, 57668
    - Miscellaneous-Publicity Photos, undated; 57673 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Foundry at University of Tehran, 1965; 57672 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Tanavoli Bronze-Pahlavi University, Shraz, Iran, 1969; 57671 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Tanavoli with 2 children, 1975; 57670 (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - Tanavoli Art work, undated; 57669 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Subseries G: Artwork, 57663
    - Grey Collection Art, undated; 57667 (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - Guinis, Alkis (Greek Artist), undated; 57666 (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - Padamsee, Akbar (Indian Artist), undated; 57665 (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous Artwork (Seichrist, Ron), undated; 57664 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Subseries H: Miscellaneous, 57651
    - Contact Sheets, undated; 57662 (Box 41, Folder 17)
    - Miscellaneous Snapshots, Nov 4, 1965; 57661 (Box 41, Folder 18)
    - Miscellaneous Snapshots, Nov 10, 1965; 57660 (Box 41, Folder 19)
    - Miscellaneous Snapshots, Nov 23, 1965; 57659 (Box 41, Folder 20)
    - Miscellaneous Snapshots, Dec 1, 1965; 57658 (Box 42, Folder 1)
      3 1142 04225405 5
    - Student Sculpture Party, Feb 1, 1968; 57657 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Traveling with the Bishop of Iran (Evangelism in a Moslem world), 1974; 57656 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Blind Students of Braille School, Isfahan, Iran, undated; 57655 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous Snapshots, undated; 57654 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous, undated; 57653 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous, undated; 57652 (Box 42, Folder 7)